icevonline.com 2017-02-22

# Privacy Policy | iCEV Online CTE Curriculum

**  
What Information is Collected?**  
The personally identifiable information collected on iCEV is minimal. For teachers, we collect the following information: name, login credentials, email address and one security question. For students, we collect the following information: name, login credentials and one security question. We do not collect information about a user other than information that is voluntarily provided.

**What We Do With the Collected Information?  
** We utilize the collected information to provide service to iCEV users. We utilize security questions to reset forgotten login credentials after following reset protocol. We utilize the teacher's email address to send our newsletter which contains information regarding new features and new lessons added to iCEV. Each newsletter provides the teacher the opportunity to opt out of further email communication.

**What We DO NOT Do With the Collected Information  
** We do not sell, share or rent personal information of teachers or students. We do not utilize teacher or student information for behavioral targeting of advertisements. We do not utilize student information to build personal profiles of a student. We do not allow any CEV employees to access student data unless they have undergone a strenuous criminal background check as well as professional development on handling sensitive data.

**How Long Is Information Retained?**  
We will not keep personal information longer than the time frame necessary to support the purpose of the contract or as authorized by the parent/student. At any time an educational institution, parent or authorized person wishes to delete personal information, they may do so by contacting customersupport@cevmultimedia.com.

**How is Information Protected?  
** The security of personal information is important to us. When entering sensitive information on our registration form, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect personal information submitted, both during transmission and once received. In the event of a breach of personal information we will alert the educational institution's main CEV contact within 24 hours of confirmation of breach. If you have any questions about the security of our website, you can request more information by emailing customersupport@cevmultimedia.com.

**Contact Information**  
CEV Multimedia, Ltd. is located at 1020 SE Loop 289, Lubbock, TX, 79423. You may contact us at customersupport@cevmultimedia.com, phone (800) 922-9965.
